>> Brian Holt: 好的，这真是太恶心了
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: All right this is really
feeling gross to write this inside of
一个脚本标签，每个人在里面都觉得恶心吗 ?
a script tag, does everyone
feel sufficiently gross inside?
太好了我想让你今天早上感觉好
Good, that’s what I wanted
you to feel this morning.
所以我想让你打开一个叫 App.js 的文件
So what I want you to do is I want
you to open a file called App.js,
把它放在同一个源目录里
just put it in the same source directory.
在这一点上，我也想指出一点。
One thing I wanted to point
out at this point as well.
反应极为灵活。
React is extremely flexible.
几乎什么都不是很规范的。
It's not very prescriptive at
all about pretty much anything.
我喜欢这样因为它能让我做出技术上的决定
I like this because it allows me
to make technical decisions for
我自己也不依赖别人的技术决定，
myself and not rely on
the technical decisions of others,
但那是我的哲学对吧
but that's a philosophy that I have,
right?
你不一定要分享这一点。
And you don't necessarily
have to share that.
这意味着我们可以组织我们的项目但是 React 不关心
Which means we can organize our project
however we want, React doesn't care,
对于如何组织项目， React 具有零意见。
React has zero opinions on the matter
of how you organize your project.
为了简单起见，我组织了这个项目，它不是一个非常大的项目。
I have organized this project just for
simplicity, it's not a very big project.
所以我不是说我们要结束的这个回购协议
So, I'm not saying that this repo
that we're gonna end up with is
很有组织的组织我只会说很简单
incredibly well organized,
I'm just gonna say it's simple.
所以这就是我想扔的地方
So that's one thing I
wanted to throw out there,
这不是我要教你参加这个讲习班的事
that's not something I'm intending
to teach you with this workshop.
好了把所有东西都从你的剧本里拿过来
Okay, so take everything from your
script tag here, cut that out, and
把这个放在你的应用程序里
put this inside of your app.
删除该注释。
Delete that comment as well.
说吧
Say that.
返回到 index.html 并放入 src ="./App.js"。
Go back over to your index.html and
put your src ="./App.js".
>> Brian Holt: 好的，我所做的都是把整个剧本都剪掉了
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay, so all I did was cut
that entire script out of the source here
我把它放在 app.JS 里面
and I put that inside of app.JS.
> > Brian Holt: 下一步我们要做的就是创建
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Next thing we're
gonna do is we're going to create
另一个组件。
another component.
>> Brian Holt: 我们会说 const Pet = 另一个箭头
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: We're gonna
say const Pet = another arrow
功能 >> Brian Holt: 我要去
function
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: I'm going
以返回 React.createElement。
to return React.createElement.
>> Brian Holt: 另一个区
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Another div.
>> Brian Holt: 另一个空对象，其中一个数组和
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Another empty object,
and inside of that another array and
我们会很快地描述一个宠物
we're going to describe
a pet very quickly.
>> Brian Holt: 因此我要说的是 reacet.createElement。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So
I'm gonna say react.createElement.
让它成为 h2让它成为我的笔记
Gonna make this an h2, lets make it
an h1 actually cuz that's my notes have,
空的物体你可以把你的宠物的名字放在那里
empty object and you can put
whatever your pet's name is there,
我的名字叫卢娜好吗
mine's name is Luna, okay?
> > Brian Holt: 然后我在这里放 3 条不同的线
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And then I'm gonna put
three different lines in here, and
这会是一个 h1 和两个 h2的
this is gonna be an h1 and two h2's.
Luna 是一只狗，她的品种是 " 哈瓦南人 " 。
And Luna is a Dog, and
her breed is Havanese.
>> Brian Holt: 我在这里又创造了一个邮票，对吧 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So
I've created another stamp here, right?
我没用过邮票，但我去了店，买了一个
I have not used the stamp but I've gone
to the store and I've purchased one and
我只是有点握着它没做任何事
I'm just kinda holding it,
not doing anything with it yet.
>> Brian Holt: 好的，在这里，在应用中，我要把它变成一个阵列
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay, so here, inside of
App, I'm gonna make this into an array so
我可以把多个孩子放进去
I can put multiple children in it.
> > Brian Holt: 在这里，让我们把这个看起来好。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And here,
let's make this look nice.
>> Brian Holt: 我将放置三个宠物项目实例。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: I'm gonna put
three instances of the pet item.
>> Brian Holt: 因此我要放入 React.createElement Pet，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So
I'm gonna put React.createElement Pet,
那我就把这三遍都放了
then I'm gonna put this three times.
> > Brian Holt: 现在注意，我不会把其他东西放进去。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Now notice I'm not putting
the rest of the stuff in there as well.
如果你想的话你可以的
You can if you want to.
您可以放置空的对象和空的数组或类似的内容。
You can put empty object and
empty array or something like that.
你不必这么做
You don't have to.
这是选修会
It's optional.
如果你不给它就假设它没有属性
If you don't give it anything, it just
assumes that it has no attributes and
没有孩子。
has no children.
> > Brian Holt: 所以我做了一个橡皮图章，我给了它三次，对吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So I made a rubber stamp,
and I stamped it three times, right?
那么现在，你希望看到什么呢 ?
So now, what do you expect
to see when we render this?
我想看一下 div 对吧
Well, I expect to see a div, right?
在那个 div 里面我们看到的第一件事是 h1 然后我就去印宠物
Inside of that div, the first thing we see
is an h1, and then I'm gonna stamp Pet,
好了我要进去了我要去检查 1 号和 1 号
okay, so I'm gonna go inside of Pet here
and I'm going to inspect a div, an h1 and
两个 h2s 吧
two h2s here, right?
我要知道这个模式又重复了三遍，说明白吗 ?
And I'm gonna see that this pattern
repeated three times, make sense?
现在是 3号了如果我们进去你就该认得我了
It's now on 3, if we go in here,
you should see Adopt Me,
Luna Dog Havanese， Luna Dog Havanese， Luna Dog Havanese。
Luna Dog Havanese, Luna Dog Havanese,
Luna Dog Havanese.
>> Brian Holt: 这就是组件的酷，因为它们本质上是
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So this is what's cool
about components is they are inherently
可重复使用，对吗 ?
reusable, right?
我做了一个宠物组件，我给它盖了三次。
I made one pet component and
I stamped it three times.
>> Brian Holt: 这很酷，除了
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Which is pretty cool,
except for
这一点都不太灵活，对吧 ?
the fact that this is not
very flexible at all, right?
这不灵活
It's not flexible.
我听说除了 Luna 还有其他狗
There are other dogs besides Luna,
I'm told, so
我们可能需要让这一点变得更灵活些
we probably need to make this
a little bit more flexible.